College english test band four part two
大学英语四级考试第二部分
listening comprehension
听力理解
Section a
第A节
Directions , in this section
指导语：在本节中
You will hear three news reports
你将听到三篇新闻报道
At the end of each news report
每篇新闻报道结束后
You will hear two or three questions
你将听到两到三个问题
Both the news report and the questions will be spoken only once
新闻报道和问题均只朗读一遍
After you hear a question
听到问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选择最佳答案
B , c and d
B、C和D
then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet one
然后在答题卡一上标出相应字母
with a single line through the center
用一条横线贯穿字母中央
News report one
新闻报道一
Everything changed for seven year old to wreak
七岁的塔里克的一切都因此而改变
When he slapped some butter on an ear of corn
那天他把黄油涂在一个玉米棒上
He knew it tasted good
他知道玉米本来就好吃
But butter made it better
但黄油让它更美味了
His passion for produce got him a position as south dakotta's
他对农产品的热情让他获得了一个职位，成为南达科他州的
Official corn ambassador to ek's profession of love for his favorite vegetable
官方玉米大使。他对这种最爱蔬菜的热情表白
Earned him the name the corn kid
为他赢得了"玉米小子"的称号
this was after his online interview attracted millions of views
这一切发生在他的网络采访视频吸引数百万次观看之后
And was made into a song
并被改编成了一首歌
South dakota is one of the top corn producers in america
南达科他州是美国顶级玉米产地之一
The corn provides nourishment across the globe
这里的玉米为全球各地提供营养
To riek said
塔里克说道
Not everyone has to like corn
不是每个人都必须喜欢玉米
But everyone should definitely try it , especially with butter
但每个人都绝对应该尝一尝，特别是加了黄油的
Tarek and his family were invited to south dakota
塔里克和他的家人受邀前往南达科他州
To attend the honorary ceremony at the state's . corn palace
参加在该州玉米宫殿举行的荣誉仪式
Officials wanted to highlight south dakotta's two largest industries
官员们希望借此宣传南达科他州的两大主要产业
Tourism and agriculture
旅游业和农业
to reek couldn't believe his eyes
塔里克简直不敢相信自己的眼睛
When he saw the palace made of corn
当他看到那座由玉米构成的宫殿时
questions one and two are based on the news report you have just heard
第一题和第二题基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question one
第一题
how did terriek make corn taste better
塔里克是怎样让玉米变得更好吃的？
question two
第二题
why were to riek and his family invited to south dakota
塔里克和他的家人为何受邀前往南达科他州？
News report two
新闻报道二
Two arrests were announced thursday
周四宣布了两起逮捕行动
The arrests were in connection with a string of male thefts from us
此次逮捕与一系列针对美国
post services collection boxes in marion county
邮政服务信箱的邮件盗窃案有关，案发地在马里恩县
And for the possession of a stolen postal key
还涉及持有一把被盗邮政钥匙的指控
According to the department of justice
据司法部表示
Jordan jacks and tarred goodman
乔丹·杰克斯和塔德·古德曼
Both twenty three , were arrested after evidence gathered in an investigation
两人均为二十三岁，在调查中收集到的证据
Showed the pair stole mail on multiple occasions using a postal key
显示两人多次利用邮政钥匙盗取邮件后被捕
According to a news release
据新闻通稿显示
Jack and goodman stole mail for around four months
杰克斯和古德曼盗取邮件长达约四个月
Investigators reviewed videos of the collection boxes
调查人员查看了信箱的监控录像
The video showed the two men loading the stolen mail into jackson's vehicle
视频显示两名男子将盗取的邮件装入杰克斯的车辆中
Investigators were also able to recover the key that was used to open the collection boxes
调查人员还找回了用于打开信箱的那把钥匙
jack and goodman each face up to five years in federal prison in the male theths
杰克斯和古德曼每人因邮件盗窃罪面临最高五年联邦监禁
And up to ten years for possession of the postal key
以及因持有邮政钥匙面临最高十年监禁
Questions three and four are based on the news report you have just heard
第三题和第四题基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question three
第三题
What did jordan jacks and tarred goodman do
根据新闻通稿，乔丹·杰克斯和塔德·古德曼做了什么？
According to a news release
据新闻通稿显示
question four
第四题
what do jordan jack's and troid goodman face
乔丹·杰克斯和特洛伊德·古德曼将面临什么？
News report three
新闻报道三
Can fast fashion be sustainable
快时尚能否实现可持续发展？
Researchers think yes
研究人员认为可以
identifying why the fast fashion business model creates waste
找出快时尚商业模式造成浪费的原因
And determining whether regulators can establish incentives for consumers and manufacturers
以及确定监管机构是否能为消费者和制造商建立相应激励机制
Are steps to reduce waste
是减少浪费的重要步骤
Recently , the clothing industry has come under attack for creating a waste problem
近来，服装行业因制造浪费问题而备受批评
With serious environmental consequences
并带来了严重的环境后果
In the absence of environmentally and economically feasible recycling options
在缺乏环保且经济可行的回收方案的情况下
Fast fashion manufacturers pump out low quality clothes
快时尚制造商大量生产低质量服装
Produced in high volumes that are worn only a few times and then discarded
这些衣物产量高，却只穿几次便被丢弃
the researchers put forth policy contributions ranging from sustainable
研究人员提出了一系列政策建议，涵盖从可持续
Disposal of leftover stock to production tax
处置滞销库存到征收生产税等方面
Ten centivize both manufacturers and consumers to be more waste conscious
以激励制造商和消费者更加注重减少浪费
In order to devise effective policies to curb the environmental impact of the clothing industry
为了制定有效政策以遏制服装行业对环境的影响
It is important to identify the source of the problem in the supply chain
找出供应链中问题的根源至关重要
Manufacturers , consumers and regulatory bodies can then take an informed approach
这样，制造商、消费者和监管机构才能采取有据可查的方式
to recognize the environmental impact of fast fashion
认识快时尚对环境的影响
And to design an ecosystem to reduce waste
并共同设计一套减少浪费的生态体系
Incentivize innovation and create new business models to manage waste
激励创新并创建新商业模式来管理废物
Questions five to seven are based on the news report you have just heard
第五题至第七题基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question five
第五题
Why has the clothing industry come under attack
服装行业为何备受批评？
question six
第六题
why do the researchers put forth such policies as production tax
研究人员为何提出生产税等此类政策？
question seven
第七题
What should be done first
应首先采取什么措施
to eliminate the harm caused by the clothing industry
来消除服装行业造成的危害？
Section b directions , in this section
第B节指导语：在本节中
You will hear two long conversations
你将听到两段长对话
At the end of each conversation
每段对话结束后
You will hear four questions
你将听到四个问题
Both the conversation and the questions will be spoken only once
对话和问题均只朗读一遍
After you hear a question
听到问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选择最佳答案
B , c and d
B、C和D
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet one with a single line through the center
然后在答题卡一上用一条横线贯穿字母中央标出相应字母
Conversation one
对话一
Hey mary
嘿，玛丽
You seem to be very much annoyed
你看起来很生气
What happened
发生什么事了？
Rush hour in this city is killing me
这座城市的上下班高峰期快把我逼疯了
Ah yes
啊，是的
Rush hour is terrible
高峰期确实很糟糕
Especially in the morning between eight and nine
尤其是早上八点到九点之间
But what else can you expect in a city this big
但这么大的城市，你还能期望什么呢？
Well
嗯
I think the local government could help improve things
我认为地方政府可以帮助改善这种情况
I mean , getting rid of rush hour may be impossible
我是说，消除高峰期可能是不现实的
But it could be made more tolerable
但可以让它变得更容易忍受
Don't you think
你不觉得吗？
Um
嗯……
But i'm not sure how
但我不确定该怎么做
Well , for example , the subway system could have air conditioning
比如，地铁系统可以安装空调
I know many cities in the world
我知道世界上很多城市
Have air conditioning in their subway
地铁里都有空调
So why can't we
那我们为什么不能有呢？
It gets so hot in the summer
夏天地铁里太热了
I can hardly breathe down there
我在那里面几乎喘不过气来
And add to that the rush hour crowds with strangers
再加上高峰期那些陌生人
Packed close together in the subway carriages
挤在地铁车厢里
The whole thing is just horrible
整件事简直太可怕了
Ah yes
啊，是的
You are completely right
你说得完全正确
The trains here are too old
这里的列车太老旧了
The government should definitely invest in new ones with air conditioning
政府绝对应该投资购买带空调的新列车
I guess i'm fortunate i take the bus instead
我想我很幸运，我乘公共汽车上班
Oh that's much better
哦，那好多了
Yeah , it's more convenient
是的，更方便
Bus number thirty six go straight from my house to the office
36路公共汽车直接从我家开到办公室
It's a thirty minute ride and i don't have to make any changes
坐三十分钟，不需要换乘
That sounds nice
听起来不错啊
I tell you my current commute is killing me
我告诉你，我现在的通勤真的快把我搞垮了
Maybe i should move closer to the office
也许我应该搬到离公司更近的地方
Well i know a great housing agent
嗯，我认识一个很棒的房产中介
I found the flat i'm living in now through him and i love it
我现在住的公寓就是通过他找到的，我很喜欢
Mm could you send me his number please
嗯……你能把他的电话号码发给我吗？
Sure thing
没问题
Just tell him exactly what you are looking for
只要告诉他你在找什么样的房子
And i'm sure he will find something good
我相信他一定能找到合适的
Questions eight to eleven are based on the conversation you have just heard
第八题至第十一题基于你刚才听到的对话
Question eight
第八题
Why is the woman complaining
这位女士为何在抱怨？
question nine
第九题
what does the woman suggest doing
这位女士建议怎么做？
question ten
第十题
what do we learn about the man from the conversation
从对话中我们了解到关于这位男士的什么信息？
question eleven
第十一题
What does the woman ask the man to do
在对话结尾，这位女士请男士做什么？
at the end of the conversation
在对话结束时
Conversation two
对话二
Did you hear about johnny
你听说约翰尼的事了吗？
No , why is he okay
没有，他没事吧？
He had some plastic surgery done
他做了整形手术
What
什么？
Why do you remember
你记得吗
He had a scar on his face
他脸上有一道疤
Yes , of course he always had that
是的，当然，他一直都有那道疤
I've known him since primary school
我从小学就认识他了
And i always remember him having that on his cheek
我一直记得他脸颊上有那道疤
Well
嗯
He had it fixed
他把它修复了
Fixed
修复了？
What do you mean
什么意思？
You can't fix a scar
疤怎么能修复呢？
You know what i mean
你明白我的意思
He had an operation done on it
他做了一个手术
Plastic surgery in order to cover it and make it less noticeable
做了整形手术，为了遮盖它，让它不那么明显
Oh well , that's ridiculous , isn't it
哦，这不是很可笑吗？
It was noticeable , sure
那道疤确实很明显
But it wasn't an ugly scar
但它不是一道难看的疤
It never occurred to me that he should have it taken care of like that
我从来没想到他需要这样去处理它
I agree
我同意
I can understand some scars and physical defects can be ugly and distracting
我能理解有些疤痕和身体缺陷可能是难看的，令人分心的
But not johnny's in fact
但约翰尼的不是。事实上
I thought it added character like it gave him a certain uniqueness
我认为那道疤给了他一种独特的个性，赋予了他某种独特魅力
He must have felt differently
他肯定有不同的感受
Though he must have felt self conscious and insecure . perhaps
他可能感到自我意识过强，不够自信，也许吧
No , no , that's not the reason
不，不，那不是原因
He was totally fine with his scar
他对自己的疤痕完全没问题
As you said , he had had it for most of his life
就像你说的，那道疤伴随了他大半辈子
Then why did he have the operation
那他为什么要做这个手术呢？
Because his girlfriend wanted him to what
因为他女朋友想让他做——什么？
That's so superficial and selfish of her
她太肤浅、太自私了
If johnny's girlfriend doesn't like him for who he is
如果约翰尼的女朋友不接受他本来的样子
Then she does not deserve to be his girlfriend
那她就不配做他的女朋友
You're right
你说得对
So he is insane to give to her like that
所以他向她妥协真是太疯狂了
But when i told him
但当我告诉他这些时
He said he loves her and would just do what she wants him to
他说他爱她，会顺她的心意去做
What a fool he is
他真是个傻瓜
Questions twelve to fifteen are based on the conversation you have just heard
第十二题至第十五题基于你刚才听到的对话
Question twelve
第十二题
What does the man say about johnny
这位男士关于约翰尼说了什么？
question thirteen
第十三题
what does the woman find puzzling
这位女士觉得哪件事令人费解？
question fourteen
第十四题
what did the man think of johnny scar
这位男士对约翰尼的疤痕有什么看法？
question fifteen
第十五题
how could we describe the speaker's attitude towards johnny's girlfriend
如何描述说话者对约翰尼女朋友的态度？
Section c
第C节
Directions
指导语
In this section you will hear three passages
在本节中，你将听到三篇短文
At the end of each passage
每篇短文结束后
You will hear three or four questions
你将听到三到四个问题
Both the passage and the questions will be spoken only once
短文和问题均只朗读一遍
After you hear a question
听到问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选择最佳答案
B , c , and d
B、C和D
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer
然后在答题卡
Sheet one with a single line through the center passage one
一上用一条横线贯穿字母中央标出相应字母。第一篇短文
Talking is unique to humans
语言是人类所独有的
An animal might make ten different sounds
动物可能发出十种不同的声音
But an adult human knows more than twenty thousand words
但一个成年人知道的单词超过两万个
Additionally , with the only animal that expresses thoughts in full sentences
此外，我们是唯一能用完整句子表达思想的动物
Researchers don't think language was invented
研究人员认为语言并非发明出来的
Instead , they think it's evolved
而是认为它是进化而来的
How did talking evolve
语言是如何进化的？
There are two main theories
主要有两种理论
The first theory is that language started with people making different sounds
第一种理论认为语言起源于人们发出不同的声音
Mostly imitating the things around them like animal calls
主要是模仿周围的事物，比如动物的叫声
Nature sounds , and the sounds of tools
自然界的声音以及工具发出的声音
Perhaps they made the sound of wind to comment on the weather
也许他们模拟风声来描述天气状况
Or imitated the sound of a bird to tell a friend that there was a bird nearby
或者模仿鸟叫声告诉朋友附近有一只鸟
Then , over hundreds of thousands of years
然后，经过数十万年的演变
Those sounds turned into words that people began to learn as part of their language
那些声音逐渐演变成了单词，人们开始将其作为语言的一部分学习
At some point , people started stringing the words together to form sentences
在某一时刻，人们开始把单词组合在一起，形成句子
The other main theory
另一种主要理论
Which is more recent , is that people started off by gesture ing
时间更近，认为人们最初通过手势进行交流
Pointing at things with their hands
用手指向事物
And imitating actions using their bodies
并用身体模仿动作
Eventually , these gestures turned into full sign language
最终，这些手势演变成了完整的手语
This theory guesses that after developing sign languages
这个理论推测，在发展出手语之后
People eventually started making sounds along with their gestures
人们最终开始在手势的同时发出声音
At some point they switched to mostly making sounds that became words
在某一时刻，他们转向主要通过声音来表达，声音演变成了语言
Instead of just using their bodies
而不再仅仅依靠肢体动作
The reason they switched to making sounds
他们之所以转向发出声音
The theory goes is that talking out loud
该理论认为是因为大声说话
Lets you communicate with someone
可以让你和某人交流
Even when you can't see them
即使你看不见对方
Questions sixteen to eighteen are based on the passage you have just heard
第十六题至第十八题基于你刚才听到的短文
Question sixteen
第十六题
How did language come into being according to researchers
据研究人员说，语言是如何产生的？
question seventeen how did language start according to the first theory
第十七题：根据第一种理论，语言是如何起源的？
question eighteen
第十八题
Why did people switch from gesturing to making sounds
根据较新的理论，人们为什么从手势交流转向发出声音？
according to the more recent theory
根据这一较新理论
Passage two
第二篇短文
Is it a good idea to display luxury brands and other signals of status
展示奢侈品牌和其他地位象征是否是个好主意？
It depends on the situation
这取决于具体情况
Studies have shown that people who appear to be wealthy
研究表明，看起来有钱的人
Tend to be considered more intelligent
往往被认为比没有这种表现的人更聪明
Disciplined , and competent than those who do not
更自律，更有能力
But new research found that people believe someone who shows off their social status
但新研究发现，人们认为那些炫耀社会地位的人
Cares more about benefiting themselves than helping others
更关心从中获利而非帮助他人
This means people are less willing to collaborate with them
这意味着人们不太愿意与他们合作
Modesty may be key when cooperation is essential
在需要合作的场合，谦逊可能是关键
But the researchers also found that in some cases , status signaling has advantages
但研究人员也发现，在某些情况下，展示地位是有优势的
Experiments showed that participants were less likely to choose someone
实验表明，参与者不太可能选择
Who signals their wealth or status to join a group seeking cooperative members
那些炫耀财富或地位的人加入寻求合作成员的团队
But participants were more likely to choose that person
但参与者更倾向于选择该人
When they were looking for a competitive team member
当他们在寻找具有竞争力的团队成员时
These findings suggest that people should change how they present themselves
这些发现表明，人们应该根据自己的社交目标
Depending on their social goal
调整自己的呈现方式
This is the era of social media
这是社交媒体时代
People can easily share their wealth and status to large audiences
人们可以轻松地向大量受众展示自己的财富和地位
But they need to consider the consequences
但他们需要考虑其后果
Posting about luxury purchases and expensive vacations online
在网上晒奢侈品购物和昂贵假期
May help you to persuade others and frighten competitors
可能有助于你说服他人并威慑竞争对手
But it could also signal to potential friends or future employers
但也可能向潜在朋友或未来雇主传递一个信号
That you are unlikely to think about the needs of others
即你不太可能顾及他人的需求
This makes things tricky for people
这让那些想给他人留下深刻印象
Who may want to impress others
又想给人留下好印象的人感到两难
While also demonstrating that they are a team player
同时还想表明自己是团队中的一员
Question nineteen to twenty one are based on the passage you have just heard
第十九题至第二十一题基于你刚才听到的短文
Question nineteen
第十九题
How would people describe someone who shows off their social status
根据新研究，人们会如何描述一个炫耀社会地位的人？
according to new research
据新研究显示
Question twenty
第二十题
when were participants more likely to choose someone who signalled their wealth or status
参与者在什么情况下更愿意选择那些展示财富或地位的人？
Questions twenty one
第二十一题
what should people do when sharing their wealth and status online
在网上分享财富和地位时，人们应该怎么做？
Passage three
第三篇短文
Human fascination with animals goes back as far as humans do
人类对动物的迷恋可以追溯到人类本身的起源
Of the oldest cave paintings discovered
在已发现的最古老的洞穴壁画中
Some are up to forty thousand years old
有些已有多达四万年的历史
And there are more images of animals than humans
其中动物的图像多于人类的图像
At some point humans began to capture and hold animals
在某个时刻，人类开始捕捉并圈养动物
The first known collections were held by royalty
已知最早的动物收藏由皇室掌管
And were not open to the public
且不向公众开放
In egypt
在埃及
Researchers have found buildings from around three thousand five hundred bc
研究人员发现了约公元前三千五百年的建筑
Containing the remains of animals , including elephants
其中保存着动物遗骸，包括大象
Which were not native to egypt
而大象并非埃及的本地物种
But life wasn't easy for these animals
但这些动物的生活并不容易
They probably had short lives
它们寿命可能很短
And the remains show evidence of severe injuries
遗骸上显示出严重受伤的痕迹
The first public exhibit of animals
第一个公开展出动物的场所
May have been created by egypt
可能是由埃及
Queen hat chipsuit around fourteen ty bc
女王哈特谢普苏特在约公元前1400年建立的
Researchers think the zoo was started with animals
研究人员认为，这座动物园最初
Brought home from a far off land known as punt
以从一个叫庞特的遥远国度带回的动物为基础建立
It's unclear why the queen built the zoo
女王为何建造这座动物园，目前尚不清楚
But it might have been to show off her wealth and power
但可能是为了彰显她的财富和权力
Early zos are found all over the world in china
早期的动物园遍布世界各地。在中国
Emperor when wang is said to have built a garden of intelligence around ten sixty bc
相传周文王在约公元前1060年建造了一座"灵囿"
It included deer , birds and many fish
其中饲养有鹿、鸟类和众多鱼类
In england , king henry the first set up a collection of animals in about eleven ten
在英国，亨利一世国王于约1110年在皇家庄园内
As part of the royal estate
建立了一处动物收藏地
His collection included tigers and lions
其中包括老虎和狮子
This collection eventually moved to the tower of london in twelve thirty five
这处收藏最终于1235年迁移至伦敦塔
The collection stayed at that location for six hundred years
这批动物在那里保存了六百年
Questions twenty two to twenty five are based on the passage you have just heard
第二十二题至第二十五题基于你刚才听到的短文
Question twenty two
第二十二题
What can we see in the oldest cave paintings
在最古老的洞穴壁画中可以看到什么？
Question twenty three
第二十三题
what do we learn about the first known collections of animals
关于最早已知的动物收藏，我们了解到什么？
Question twenty four
第二十四题
what might be the reason the egyptian queen created the zoo
埃及女王建造动物园的原因可能是什么？
Question twenty five
第二十五题
What do we learn about king henry
关于亨利一世
the first collection of animals in england
英国第一批动物收藏，我们了解到什么？
that's the end of listening comprehension
听力理解部分到此结束